Friends with beer?
[
My god that's a long modem. I was just gonna say that takes a long time to connect.
I have a shorter one.
Of course after listening to the first one and then me playing that
anyone can be forgiven for not feeling like it was shorter.
Yeah, I think we should go with the quicker connect times next time. You know, if we just
connect at like 300 baud, I think that's fine. We don't need to wait for the 56k VDOT, you know,
whatever. VDOT insert protocol here. What was it? What? V.35? Is that what I'm thinking of?
There was V.56. There was VDOT...
There was VDOT something else. V.56 was the one that went
went ba-dong ba-dong bong bong bong yeah i remember that sound like a twanging sound
yep there was another v.fast or v.everything you know there were a few of those well i
think v.fast was what originally got ousted and well i can't remember is v.everything
supported that and v.54 56 yeah i think v.fast and v.56 were two competing standards and
eventually v.56 won anyway we haven't even talked about who we are let's pretend this
the first one because in all honesty me going back and trying to salvage what we've done
before seems highly unlikely if this sounds good at all yeah wait are you talking about previous
recordings of this episode of this show or are you talking about previous podcasts that we've done
both okay because either one seems equally applicable yeah i'm going to delete anything
with our voices on it that i can find that's a lot of podcasts hi i'm scott willsey and this is
This is Peter Nikolaidis, my friend.
What's up?
We are friends with beer.
We're also friends with each other.
We've been friends with each other probably longer than we've known that we're friends
with beer.
So, yeah, I guess, I mean, that's a bit of a play on the name of the title of the podcast,
but I had thought that the title would be like "Friends..."
Comma with beer?
Comma with beer, not that we are friends with beer.
Right.
But here's the problem.
think a lot of Americans understand the distinction if I might be so bold as to
potentially insult some of our listeners. And you might. Mm-hmm. Okay. Well, go ahead.
Potentially insult them. Oh, no, I don't think that a lot of people understand
the distinction. And a podcast title looks a hell of a lot better without a
comma, so. Yeah, well, I got that. I'm pouring. So I already opened my bottle a
while ago because it needed to warm up some. Oh, that's the opposite of problem
people usually have beer but i guess you had yours in the freezer no i had it in the refrigerator but
this is a beer that is best drunk at around 50 degrees i don't think beer should get drunk
i think the people drinking the beer see here we go again with the comma oh sorry this beer is best
comma drunk at 50 degrees what's the comma saves lives joke i don't remember i don't know all i
remember i only remember the one about helping your uncle jack off his horse yeah well there's
There's one where if you don't use the comma the kid dies. I don't remember.
Well, anyways, tonight my beer after I threatened to for several episodes, which are in the
can apparently.
Okay, just to remind the listener, Peter Nikolaidis is about to state his beer.
A double chocolate three philosophers from Ommegang Brewery in Cooperstown, New York.
And this is one of my favorite beers of all time. And the reason is this is like an event
for me. I can't just drink one of these because it's 9.7% alcohol. Right. So this is a commitment.
So I've pretty much trashed the entire evening dedicated to this beer and this podcast. So
I hope you and you, dear listener, appreciate the sacrifice I am about to make. So to you,
cheers. Peter, not only do I appreciate the sacrifice that you've made with your beer
your friendship and your time. I appreciate the sacrifice that you made with your effort
to get set up for this recording. I really do. I really appreciate that. Now, I'm Scott
Wilsey again in case the people haven't learned our voices yet. I'm the one who was charitably
described by a listener to a different podcast of mine as the nerdy sounding guy.
Well, I mean that's a step up, right? That's a step up from a voice for print, right?
Well, he went on to say other things, but I won't repeat them here.
Oh, well, he started off, you know, gentle.
He started off with the best.
It's kind of blurry.
Can you hold it up like right in front of your face?
Yeah.
And back it up a little bit.
This is a three creeks, five pine chocolate porter.
So it's interesting, three creeks as in C-R-E-E-K-S?
Right, that's right.
Because this is a, let me see, this combination,
this is a blend of a Belgian quadruple and a creek ale.
K-R-I-E-K.
K-R-I-E-K?
Yeah, it's a type of, like a fruity type of beer.
I didn't know that.
So we both got chocolate, we both got creek.
Bingo, exactly.
And that was not planned.
No, it was not.
Which is kind of cool.
Now what's awesome though is this beer is something
that is best enjoyed with some fine foods.
So to go with it.
Oh wow, you're on me.
I have some cherries.
Oh my gosh.
Dark red cherries.
Peter, you're romancing yourself tonight, aren't you?
And well, I am alone tonight. Well with you, but anyway,
and some dark chocolate covered almonds.
Those are beautiful.
They are, and they're going to pair very well with this beer. So anyway,
this is the, a very limited edition dark chocolate,
double chocolate roasted version. And they coincidentally,
they use Taza chocolate, which is based right here in Somerville,
Massachusetts, one town over from me. So like I said,
this is just not a beer though. It's not a beer that is taste.
You don't just pull this out of the fridge and crack it open because number one, it's
too warm and number two, it's best served with some kind of good tasting food.
So, on that note, I'm going to eat a cherry and have a sip of beer and I'll let you talk
for a bit.
Well, I'm so glad that when you started your sentence with "pull this" that it didn't
go where I thought it was going.
I'm glad that it was just pulling it out of your fridge.
You should never pull your beer out of where I thought you were going to pull it out of.
Yeah, so let's talk a little bit about this podcast because apparently this is episode
one even though it's like episode three but you know what everyone needs a an unreleased back
catalog that shall never see the light of day and a lot of people might argue that our released
catalog should never see the light of day but this is a podcast in which peter and i get together we
have a nice conversation we have been friends for many years and we don't get to talk as much as we
like so we have been talking and we thought let's do a podcast out of it we've done lots of other
podcast Peter as all of his fans know we were just dealing with his fans a minute ago we had
to push them off to one side his fans know that he was on the fresh Ubuntu podcast yes back in the
day we had 10,000 listeners when 10,000 listeners was actually a thing and what were you galactic
overlord supreme i was nominated supreme galactic overlord yeah i'd have to go back and find those
exact episodes where um zerg challenged me to a fistfight that was kind of interesting
Didn't you have something about the geek-the technology in your title too, though? What was it?
Probably. Honestly, I'd have to go back and listen to some of those episodes.
Sorry, I'm eating another cherry on it now.
And now you currently have a podcast that is still active called Blurring the Lines.
Correct. That one is one that I co-host with my friend Adam Bell.
That's right.
And he's down in Nashville, Tennessee. You, however, are up on the left coast.
I am on the best coast. You're on the best coast. I'm on the least coast. And Adam is one hour
closer towards you. Right, now here's the thing. I'm-the jokes is just jokes. The jokes, the japes,
the hilarities about the coasts. I don't really care, although I like kind of where I live,
I guess. I have to live somewhere. Apparently I do. I'm a mortal being with a body. But I have a
friend that lives in Kentucky who I do a lot of podcasting with and he they try
him and Clay try to convince me that the Eastern time zone is the one true time
zone now I think they're off by five exactly anything that is an offset of
zero it seems like I don't know how you can even begin to justify that argument
like I can sum it up in one word America oh okay well there's three a words I was
thinking of that could have applied.
Let's get the third one.
I did throw together a few topics, but unlike our other podcasts, which are more structured,
this is just like, you know, whatever.
If we remember to talk about them, great.
Because generally when with friends with beer, conversation just kind of tends to happen.
It does, yeah.
A lot of times.
And then somebody inevitably ends up with their face in the peanut bowl.
Right.
For me, actually, it's dark chocolate covered almonds today,
not peanuts, but you know, that might happen.
Okay, either way your face is gonna be here nuts.
(laughing)
So I did my first Bikram yoga class for a long time today.
Pete is a yoga instructor, by the way.
Oh, I am a yoga instructor, by the way,
but I have not done Bikram for several years.
Explain your Bikram to me.
Well, actually I found an online class
and I figured since it was 90 degrees
and I wanted to be outside,
why don't I do a hot yoga class outside? So that's what I did today.
Okay. When I hear the term hot yoga, I get really afraid.
I feel like there's a crossover between people that do hot yoga and
people that get caught up in a wild internet sting of child molesters.
Am I wrong? Okay.
I can't say that you're completely wrong because there is,
there has been an intersection, but first off, hot yoga,
Generally, not always, but generally what we know today as hot yoga came out of what
was known or is known as Bikram yoga. Bikram yoga was founded by this dude, Bikram Chaudhary.
So also, dear listener, the first thing to go when I'm drinking a good beer is my speech
gets a little bit woo, and that's already happening because this is a strong beer.
I'm the same way and it's proof that I've never been drunk on the job because I would
never be able to hide it.
So Bikram founded Bikram Yoga, which is this sequence, and it's always the same sequence
done in the same order.
Seriously?
Yeah, it is.
There's no variation?
No, no variation.
Do they also refer to that as a vinyasa?
No, it is not vinyasa.
Vinyasa is different.
It's similar, but it's different.
Ashtanga Yoga also is a fixed sequence, and that's where vinyasas came from.
But anyway, Bikram yoga is generally done in like, I think it's 105 degree, supposed
to be an indoor 105 degree heated studio. Bikram frankly is a scumbag and a womanizer,
guilty, well not guilty, accused of multiple counts of sexual assault, lots of really not
shady but completely underhanded business practices. And he fled the country.
Okay, so he was I thought you said something about a woman then I thought you were saying the woman was no
He was a womanizer idolatry or whatever you say. So no womanizer him so
Okay, no idolatry
So he took like a bunch of his Rolls Royces over to back to india and uh fled the country a few years ago
Wait, was this guy called Rajneesh by any chance? No. No, that's someone else
so anyway, so um, so that said his yoga sequence I I still kind of like and i'm
not one of those people who throws the, I guess, the bathwater out with the baby in this case.
I don't know if it's reversed. There are a lot of people who condemn him for his actions, which...
Rightly so.
I stand by.
Yep.
But then, you know, there's other good that he did by bringing, you know,
he did help popularize yoga in the United States.
Oh, now it's starting to become clear to me.
Right. So he was like with, I don't even remember now, again,
beers kicking in, might've been Jane Fonda, um, Madonna.
He was like the yoga teacher teacher to a number of stars in Hollywood and he
just kind of cleaned up over there and that's how he became super duper popular.
Gotcha. But it's also how as a result,
yoga became very popular in, you know, thanks in no small parts to him.
There were essentially like half a dozen people, most of them Indian males,
who popularized yoga in the West.
And they were responsible for the major offshoots of yoga that we have today.
You had asked about vinyasa.
That came mostly from Ashtanga, which was founded by Pattabhi Joyce,
also an accused womanizer and serial sexual assaulter type of person.
Um, cough.
This is where...
See, I'm not a person that wants to know anything about actors, anything about musicians.
I don't want to know because you're always going to be sad.
These people are why.
And I am not a person that can just say, "Well, it depends, right?"
Like if they're just a kind of a jerk, whatever, but if somebody is responsible for doing really
bad things but they also have an amazing body of work. I'm not one that can really separate
that out too well. I'm going to think of it every time.
Let's say that one of them had found the cure for cancer and you had cancer and this guy
was just a complete and utter scumbag. Would you take the cure for cancer?
Oh, I would absolutely take the cure.
Right.
Because then I could live to take my revenge upon their scumbaggyness.
Well what if he was dead?
Was it me that deaded him?
No.
Oh, well that's disappointing.
Yeah.
So, that's my point though, is that in my 200 hour yoga teacher training, one of my
fellow students had been a victim of sexual abuse some time ago.
And their argument was that we should throw out anything to do with these people who committed
these heinous crimes.
And I said, if that was the case, you and I would not be here right now.
We would not be talking because two of the men who arguably are responsible for creating
the styles of yoga that led to the foundation of this studio were those guys.
So therefore we never would be here.
Maybe we would have found some other form of yoga in some other studio, but we would
not be here today if it wasn't for what they had done.
And I can say that, I believe, without elevating them to some sort of honorary pedestal. I
can separate the man from the deed.
Well, when I say that I have a hard time separating it, I don't mean because I want to put them
on a pedestal or think of them as a hero. That is definitely not it. Because if you
have people that are genuine heroes, in the sense that we like to think of, you know,
idols, heroes, whatever you want to call them.
And a lot of their students do think of them that way.
You're gonna be disappointed.
Yes.
Now, here's what I like about yoga.
I'm very new to it.
I don't even know what kind of yoga I'm doing.
I have Apple Fitness Plus.
I'm doing the yoga sessions that they have on there.
The thing about yoga is that it's friggin' amazing, man.
It has changed completely how I feel physically and it has also changed my mental approach
to life, which sounds like I'm being superlative here and making stuff up, but it actually
isn't.
It's a combination of things.
It's not just the yoga, but it has definitely made a huge difference in my physical training
regimen, like how my body feels, how my body recuperates, how my body gets ready for exercise.
All of those things are so much better now because I'm doing yoga.
That I can state 100% sure because I was doing years of the same exact training without yoga
and now I'm doing, you know, a couple, a handful of months with yoga and it's made a huge difference.
So yoga in and of itself, and I get that I'm being generic here, but it's pretty frickin'
amazing.
Like, it does make a huge difference.
So it's... it is kind of troubling that something that is so beneficial, and that does, I think,
promote mental focus, mental peace, mental quietness, the ability to start learning how
to...
I don't know if you want to say meditate, but to focus in that particular way, that
those things come from people who are obviously chaos machines.
But let me let me stop you there, though.
They popularized it and they may have refined it and stuff,
but they didn't create it. Right.
So again, it's sort of like saying
if you like hamburgers, you know, you go to a restaurant
and this guy cooks you an amazing hamburger, best burger
with a side of fries that you have ever had before.
And he serves you a beer, which is like the best beer
you have ever tasted. Right. And then you find out after you've eaten all that that
the guy was a child molester. Mm-hmm. Maybe you're never gonna go back to that
restaurant again but are you going to then swear off hamburgers and french fries
and beer never again to eat those because that guy ate them? That doesn't
make any sense. Right and it definitely helps that that person it didn't spring
from the mind of that person. Yeah. I gotta let my cat out of the room. Hold on.
That's the new cat and he's the awesome cat. He's a little blurry because of the
filter that Scott is using but he doesn't seem to want to leave the room.
Now he's left the room. You know how cats are. If the door's closed they want out.
Door's open he'll want back in as soon as he actually gets around to
going out so. So anyway yeah that was that's our philosophical discussion on yoga.
Anyway I've found it to be incredibly beneficial and it's like
anything else you really can't explain it to people you have to do it and it's
one of those things where if you try to explain you just come across as annoying
I know I've annoyed you on multiple times across the year over the years one
of my thoughts was I wished I would have listened to Peter about this a long time
ago but yeah anyway it's it's never too late to open your mind to stuff that you
for some reason didn't previously I will drink to that hmm and in fact I will
pair that with a dark chocolate-covered almond yeah oh no he's still right there
He's still right there.
Dude, he is awesome.
This cat, like we've had athletic cats before,
but this cat, his timing, his speed, his strength,
he's just a badass and he knows it too.
Sometimes he will just swat a toy right out of the air.
You fling it and you think it's going way over him
and you snap it real fast and you're right at his face
and he'll just smack it out of the air
and then he'll just go, like, is that all you got?
(laughing)
That's awesome.
Yeah, he's a good cat.
He did finally go outside. Now if you close the door he'll want to come back in.
He sure will.
Oh look at that back bend.
If I close it right now I'm good. I know he's a yoga practitioner.
All right I'm gonna try to close it.
Yep he's clear. I was gonna say use your foot. Mule kick that door shut. Good job.
There we go.
All right. So that was the main-ish fun topic. So I am eating a couple of dark chocolate
almonds right now and that is going to up my cholesterol.
I was afraid you were going to talk about stomach problems and needing to run.
No, I'm getting, well I'm taking the week off from running. This is my first rest
week in several months. My coach tells me I should
take... Stomach problems and running, I didn't mean run. I meant run.
No, not that kind. Yeah. So my running coach has told me though that I
should take one week off per month and I don't generally do that, but I'm
taking off like more like one week off per quarter or so and this is that week
because it's... Yeah, one week off a month sounds like a lot.
It does. I mean, now this guy knows what he's doing. He's done like 50 milers and stuff
like that, but I also maintain that everybody is different. So people have different needs
and different goals and intentions.
And different stages of life. You might find there are times where you do need that break
more for a while.
This is one of those times. So I'm taking the week off from running because it's just
been so bloody hot here.
People are out in the street doing yoga naked and calling it hot yoga.
hot yoga, right? But where I was going with that is I've got a blood test on Friday because
I had my first physical in about a year and a half, about a week or two, almost two weeks
ago because of COVID.
They're gonna find a lot of chocolate in your blood.
Well, they found that my cholesterol is high, which has been the case for like years. It's
always been a little bit high.
You are a healthy fit man. What's with the cholesterol? You think it's hereditary?
I think it's at least partially hereditary.
Does it change when you change your exercise regime?
Because like in 2018, when I started losing weight, my cholesterol plummeted.
All my vitals got much better.
My doctor couldn't believe it.
That's the thing is I've been in relatively same, relatively good shape for the last several
years, even though I've been running more as my principal form of exercise lately, nothing
has dramatically changed.
Like you can see my body has become a little more tone in this area and I'm a little, you
you know, thinner and that, but overall I'm still in...
I was just telling you, I wasn't going to show you.
Okay.
But my point is that I haven't changed dramatically.
Right.
You don't have a...
Like, for all we know, if you suddenly quit all of your fitness activities and you gained
40 pounds, your cholesterol might be actually lethal right now.
Who knows?
retested again, but just for kicks, I was trying to be good. This week I've been, you
know, like completely avoiding red meats. I had some turkey today. I'll probably go
all vegan except for a little bit of cream in my coffee tomorrow and just see how that
shapes up on Friday morning. See what happens, you know, how much of a variance like a few
days can make in the diet.
By the way, there are days you send me a screenshot of your food tracker. We both track our calories.
And
You will have coffee with cream for breakfast coffee with cream for lunch
And then you'll do like a 10-mile run or something and then you'll finally have dinner
And I say when and we say with cream that's usually like a teaspoon of cream, right?
But how do you do that? Like my blood sugar would be so low
Now there are times where if my blood sugar is low and I get on the bike
The first hour might be hell or the first 45 minutes or whatever. I will feel shaky
I won't be generating a lot of wattage in terms of like I'm not burning as many calories as I should be all these things and
Then I will get a second wind and I'll do okay, but it sucks compared to
Normal, so how are you a guy that doesn't have big blood sugar swings?
I don't think I do and I think that I'm probably on
Not a 24-hour cycle. I'm probably more like on a 36 to 48 hour cycle. Okay, because I have been
I've definitely gone through you know, like times where I will just fast
Without like I would I would do like coffee and that is something I've done for many years on and off
I'll just like I'll just have coffee and nothing until dinner. Yeah, for instance, but not feel hungry throughout the day
Which is the interesting part not feel like oh, yeah, I'm hitting you know, if I find
as I struggled with my weight a lot as a child into adulthood and
I find that if I'm distracted, I'm not near food and I have something else to think about then
I don't think about food. If I am bored and food is plentiful. I find myself eating a lot, right?
Yeah, yeah
So like on a day like today
My studio here is on my third floor and it's 85 degrees even with the air conditioning on. I don't work up here
I work downstairs near the kitchen
There's an abundance of food and I'm near it all the time
So that's a struggle, you know, like to have to like, "Nope, let's stay away from there." Luckily if it's a busy day at work
I'm focused on that. Otherwise, I find myself snacking a lot.
Yeah, same here.
But it's interesting because I do have the days like you're describing where I can go without food and not really think about it.
Usually what happens if I'm really busy at work and I'm deep into something
I just all of a sudden realize that I am irrationally angry and I have to go get some calories into my body.
Mm-hmm, but I do have those rare days where I literally don't care and then it's eight o'clock at night
I really haven't eaten much and I'm totally okay with it, but I can't do that on a regular basis
And I really wish I could yeah, because what I have found is the less I eat before a run the better
Performance I have the better shape. I mean I could see that I definitely there is definitely a point to like for me
Getting just enough that I'm not gonna feel that blood sugar issue during the exercise, but no more
Absolutely, right and that's the thing is like I need generally like at least an hour
after eating something light
Mm-hmm and two hours after eating something like, you know
Anything more than light and like I need a day if I had like a huge big breakfast. I'm not running
How would you write a century where you're gonna be stuffing your face on the bike once in a while?
you just have no choice because you will run out of you will bonk if you don't.
If I was doing a century, I would be doing pieces at a time, you know, 100, 100, 200 calorie Clif
bars or something as I go along. You're not going to sit down and eat a meal, although some people
go a little nuts at the break stops, but you don't have. Right, exactly. But I have found that,
I mean, if I eat a lot and this used to happen also always in the Aikido days, I would eat too
much on our lunch breaks and I come back for the afternoon class and I could barely move, you know.
Especially since people were throwing you around and your stomach was probably exactly
Very upset so I want to ask you so I mentioned to you I want to I need to vent so
Okay, this is this is my form
Cellphone carriers. Yes, sir. It's a race to the bottom when it comes to customer service
Yeah, here's what I say to cell phone carriers kiss my ass
Kiss his ass kiss your ass. Yes
bingo, so I
last
April in April I switched from a from Verizon to AT&T. Mm-hmm the V to the a and
Of course AT&T managed to completely botch the handoff as they do
They messed up the onboarding process totally and after multiple hour-long calls
I had to end up going to a store spend an hour there to get everything all squared away. Mm-hmm
Just this week. I got a letter in the mail from Verizon saying hey, we've got this great deal for Verizon FiOS customers now
I am a Verizon FiOS customer and a very happy FiOS customer
I'm not happy that I have to keep on calling them up every year or two and threaten to switch to get a better deal
Unless they give you the price you were bloody well paying before
Exactly, but other than that as far as the service goes it's been really good. Sure
So here's a deal now where they'll give me essentially the same price as what I pay for AT&T wireless right now
instead of AT&T including HBO Max
Verizon is including Disney Plus which I do pay for and Apple music which I do pay for and
Sure, it's Disney Plus premium, which includes ESPN and Hulu
so it was nice getting HBO Max, but
Until all of the the Time Warner new DC, you know
Titles start coming out next year or so. It's not something I use a lot of so I'm not really missing that but Disney Plus
I was just watching Loki before this episode
I'm big fan of all the Marvel stuff Apple music is what I use religiously because I want something I can stream to my Apple watch
Sure, so this sounds like a good deal
While I was on the phone with the woman yesterday
doing the transfer explaining to her that I
want to
you know, I need to port my number over and
I and she was going to she was taking my address down. She was verifying my address
To which they were going to send the new SIM card to use in my phone
Which I was talking to her on wait, which carrier is this? I was speaking to Verizon coming from AT&T. I
Could be mistaken, but Verizon doesn't need a SIM.
Sometimes they do. In this case it does.
And in this case, while I was talking with them, she completed the port of the number.
And the call dropped.
Oh no.
Because AT&T immediately accepted the port and I lost cell phone servers yesterday.
And I had an after-hours upgrade scheduled for work.
and my girlfriend was getting her new Tesla and I had
Insisted on not just offered I insisted on driving her to the dealership to pick it up
so I was going to be out of Wi-Fi range and
That's when Verizon decided to do this now. I'm like, it's a simple order of operations
Get the person the cell phone
Port the number right get the person the sim port the number and this rocket scientist that I was talking to
ported my number while I was on the phone with her.
Seems like a bad idea.
So the other reason though that I really moved to Verizon was that they were offering me
$700 trade-in for this one and a half year old iPhone 11 that I have.
That's pretty good I gotta say.
But I found out this yesterday, guess what? I found out. And a $300 rebate on top of that.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
So are they paying you to have a phone?
No, I needed to pay full taxes
and taxes on a $1,099 phone are like a hundred bucks.
Okay.
And I needed to pay the remaining a hundred dollars.
So I ended up paying like 150 bucks
to get an iPhone 12 Pro Max.
That is beautiful.
And here's the funny part.
That Pro Max should be here
before the stupid replacement SIM card
that they mailed me, Will.
I think what I might've been thinking about the SIM card
was that I don't remember what it was.
There was something about when we switched
from AT&T to Verizon, AT&T was all hung up on the SIM card
and it might've been locked to AT&T, I don't remember.
But when we went to Verizon, it was like,
whatever, it was totally unlocked.
You could put any SIM in there.
I think that might've been the difference.
Right, so this phone was one
that I got from Verizon in 2019.
So it's gone from Verizon to AT&T.
So they're like, "Oh, are we sure it's compatible?"
I'm like, "You guys sent it to me,
So I'm pretty sure it's compatible.
Right.
Yeah, actually it was the phone that I had before
that when we did the switchover,
this phone's always been Verizon.
But yeah, here's the thing.
Like I was gonna go back to AT&T at one point
and we're in the Apple store,
they do the verification, right?
They have to call AT&T or whoever.
And AT&T asks you a bunch of questions
and they kept asking me,
"When did you live on such and such a street?"
And I couldn't understand what they were saying.
I'm like, "I never lived on that street."
And they're like, "Okay, well, you're declined."
And I'm like, I don't know what you were saying.
Whatever you were saying is not a street that I lived on.
The funny part too, AT&T,
one of the reasons I needed to stand there for an hour
in the store was they wanted to do a credit check on me.
Even though I'm bringing my own phone.
Yes, yes, yes.
And I'm prepaying it, they wanted a credit check.
So I had to call all three credit reporting agencies
to unfreeze my credit.
Right.
while I'm on the phone, you know, while I'm standing in the store.
Verizon, they're like, "No, you're good."
Yeah, exactly, right.
The thing is, I had been an AT&T customer not that long ago,
and so I'm like, "Guys, check your records.
You will see that I paid for years.
I didn't run away. I didn't stiff you on any bills."
No, we can't do that.
Right. It's almost like their computers
can't go back in time and look at previous records.
They can't.
OK. Well, I guess you and I know nothing about computers then.
Mm-mm. We don't.
That's true.
So I'm still waiting. I have to check my email.
But the other part was...
So you're still without phone?
I am without phone.
I am without phone, but fortunately I have iMessage,
so most people can text me.
I also use RingCentral for my consultancy,
so I can make and receive phone calls at the work numbers.
Okay, okay.
But so much stuff is set up to use my cell phone number.
Yeah.
I tried to log into the Sophos partner portal,
And of course it's set to set up SMS.
Yeah, right now some package somewhere on a UPS truck
is getting authorization codes.
Right, exactly, exactly.
So I can't find anything.
And oh, my Nest thermostat, for whatever reason today,
decided it was time for me to re-authenticate
and that I had set up two-factor authentication
using my cell phone.
OMG.
So that's annoying.
The other part is like my phone hasn't shipped yet.
So it might actually be a couple days.
Wait a minute.
Not only did she do this in the wrong order,
but now they are just waddling around twiddling their thumbs
and not shipping you a phone to correct the problem.
Uh-huh.
Wow.
So what I probably will end up doing
is the same thing I did last time in 2019
after I had a horrific onboarding experience.
I'm going to call them and complain multiple times
and see if I can get better credits.
Right, but here's what you're gonna hear
on the other side of the line.
Yes, yes, I understand.
But here's the thing. I don't care.
So I got, I got, I ended up getting like 500 bucks or so of credits and discounts last time.
Yeah.
And that's the other thing. Why did I leave in the first place from AT&T?
Peter, why did you leave in the first place?
Because the Verizon plan I was on was 10 gigabytes per month shared by me and my father's cell phone and my Apple Watch.
Mm-hmm.
For the same price, AT&T gave me 100 gigabytes of LTE data.
and 30 gigs of hotspot. Now, here's the funny part. Coming back to Verizon, they're giving me
75 gigs of data and 30 gigs of hotspot. But see, that's the problem with all of these carriers,
whether it be land, internet, whether it be cellular, whatever. They always treat the
incoming people so well and they just stiff the crap out of the existing people. Which is why
every now and then it makes sense to be an outgoing/incoming person. That's right, even
even though it sucks.
It shouldn't be that way.
I would think as a business,
what you would want is a loyal customer
just in case they decide not to come back.
Yep.
And that's one of the things.
It costs a lot less to retain a customer
than it does to get a new one.
It does.
And here they are though, they're underscoring this.
They're giving us super colossal benefits and deals
all the time to win us or to win us back.
I'm like, yeah, if you just hadn't sucked
in the first place,
you wouldn't have to do any winning me back.
I'd still be here.
could make more money on you over time if they just gave you a little bit better deal
rather than having to woo you back.
Just a little.
So on that note, I am curious though, you did mention to me that you were for the first
time in a long time really excited about the Apple Worldwide Developer.
Excuse me.
Burp.
When you drink beer sometimes you burp.
No, I get excited about WWDC but...
But you said you were really excited about stuff.
So I have two questions.
Okay, I'll answer them both to the best of my ability.
And one of them you're like, this is boring,
I don't wanna talk about it.
But unrelated to this directly to WWDC though,
what do you think the next iPhone will be called?
Because they're not gonna do a 13.
Oh, I don't know.
There won't be an iPhone 13.
I don't know, maybe they will.
I don't think they will.
I don't know, maybe they'll just call it iPhone.
Maybe I don't know.
(gasps)
Maybe that's it, they dropped numbers altogether.
That's just iPhone.
I mean, that's what they do with the Mac.
And they did that with the iPad too.
Right, they do that with the iPad.
The only designation on the iPad is iPad Pro, iPad Air,
iPad, but yeah. Yeah, maybe it'll just
be iPhone.
Okay, that's my first question.
Yeah, but people have been predicting that
for a long time and it hasn't happened, so I don't know.
I don't know the answer to that question.
'Cause they did skip the nine.
Why was there no iPhone 9?
Because the eight was simultaneous with the iPhone 10.
Yeah.
It was kinda weird.
I was.
And after that, they completely dumped the,
well, I don't know, man.
Yeah.
There's no telling what's going on in the mind of Tim Apple.
Well, let's just put it this way.
Apple's been terrible with naming for a long time.
Like the Apple XS Max, that's what I have.
They're just done with names.
I mean, come on.
And then two.
And they should have known that no one would think
that it was a XS Max.
Everyone would say X.
So to most people it's an XS Max.
Which I love because again, when I was a kid growing up,
my favorite rock band was in XS.
So when I see the 10 XS, you know, I was like,
that's awesome, I love it.
It's not like they didn't know that was gonna happen
because for years people have been calling
what is now macOS that was previously macOS 10.
OS X. OS X.
People have been calling it Mac.
Yeah, people have been calling it OS X, that's right.
Yep.
So they knew that was gonna happen.
They absolutely knew that was gonna happen.
But within their super slick immaculate white walls
in Cupertino, no one ever referred to it as OSX
and therefore they did not know that was gonna happen.
No, but speaking of white walls,
I hate to put too much stock in my own criminology,
but I do believe that Jony Ive leaving Apple
was not a bad thing for Apple.
I definitely have come to that conclusion.
Post Jony Ive products are getting better again, I think.
I tend to agree.
Would you say that Jony Ive leaving Apple offsets Steve Jobs leaving Apple?
It's hard to say because I think Tim Cook started off as a really good CEO.
And he still is in some ways, but I feel like the further we get in time from the death of Steve
Jobs... Now, Steve Jobs wasn't perfect. Look, I've been following this stuff since the 70s.
I'm not one of the people that has this mythological idea about Steve Jobs, but
I mean, he was an athlete, let's just be honest.
Sure, just like Bikram. Well, maybe not a sexual offender.
Yeah, as far as we know, not that. But, nonetheless.
Right, he did try to deny his own daughter.
There's the mark of a truly great man.
But the further we get from that event, I feel like Tim Cook, and I think the bigger
and richer Apple gets, I don't like the way they portray their every business decision in such
self-righteous terms like the way they they refuse to admit that
their platform wouldn't be nearly as valuable without developers
and that they don't you know, they justify all these little business expenses
that are really nothing more than them bleeding developers dry for money
and really bad optics.
And I think Tim Cook is a lot worse about that kind of stuff than Steve Jobs was.
And I think it's getting worse over time.
And I don't know if it's because Tim Cook is getting distance between himself
than what he used to think, or if it's just because Apple's becoming a gigantic company
and they have to keep growing because, you know, they're beholden to Wall Street, just
like all American companies. And Apple's not a company that lives quarter by quarter, but
I feel like they are definitely becoming a company that has to keep impressing Wall Street
more than they used to care about.
You know, I think what turned everything around, if at the next WWDC, Phil Schiller got up
on stage and started yelling "developers developers developers developers!"
Yeah. Does he have to sweat through a shirt too?
Hell yeah!
Okay. I wonder if there's a Steve Ballmer sweat kit? Like you can just
you can just drink something and it will just make your pores ooze sweat or maybe
you just spray something on yourself.
I have a friend who sweats like that whenever he eats hot spicy foods.
Hmm. Well, I do sweat when I hot spicy food sometimes, but it's usually the head.
It's usually like my face or something.
So what I'm talking about is I had just done a 10K run and gotten in
and my friend had shown up and I had not showered or anything.
And I was, you know, like lightly sweating.
I was not gross. I was not even I need a shower.
I'm blessed by one of those things is like I do not reek when I sweat.
Right. Now, if I if I don't like shower for eight hours after I work out, that's different.
But like if I just finish a workout, I don't stick.
See, I think I sweat a lot when I exercise beyond a certain point.
Right. Well, like if I just do yoga, I don't.
Yeah. Well, it depends on the type of exercise. But like I said, I just done a 10K.
So. Right. Yeah. I would definitely need a shower. And some people might think I stink.
I personally think I smell nice and minty fresh.
I have actually been told by external parties, not myself, that I don't stink after I sweat, so it's not just me.
Do they describe you as minty?
I have been told, "Damn, you smell good," and I was said, "You know, you are, you're right. You don't stink after you work out. You're not a smelly guy."
So those are the, those are comments that I've gotten after a workout.
Do people get body parts uncomfortably close to your legs after your run?
She's cute. I wouldn't stop her. But anyway, so my friend came over and we had chicken wings and I made hot wings using various hot
sauces and after a couple of these my friend was
Drenched he had like the drenched V of sweat in the t-shirt thing going on
Oh my god, and I took pictures of the two of us side by side and I was like one of us just ran a 10k
Can you tell which?
It was pretty hilarious.
I do seem to recall an iPhone video
of you eating some hot wings one day though,
where you were getting pretty sweaty.
Oh, that was the one where I was eating,
that was the Salt Hill Pub wings challenge
up in Hanover, New Hampshire.
It was a challenge, yeah.
Yes, and I remember it 'cause I said,
it's got a good flavor,
it's too bad I can't take my time to enjoy it.
And you said you liked how I was intimidating the wing
by telling it that it tasted good.
I wanted to take my time to savor it.
I play mind games with the food, Peter.
You gotta play mind games with the food.
So on that note, I have purchased all 10 of The Hot Ones season 15 hot sauces.
Okay, I didn't know that hot sauces came in seasons.
The Hot Ones is a series.
They publish it on YouTube, among other places.
So instead of hot sauce of the month, club year, and a hot sauce of the year club?
It's they do seasons. I don't know that that's that it's annual. Mm-hmm, but they do interviews. It's a good show
They interview you can pick like some famous person that you like and they will you know
Probably have an interview by this guy Sean Evans on the hot ones and it's they eat ten
spicy hot one hot wings in increment, you know in
Exponentially increasing level of hotness and they ask interviews
So they have like off the top of my head. He's interviewed
Scarlett Johansson
Neil degrasse Tyson Shaquille O'Neal
Idris Alba. Oh my god big people. Yeah. Yeah, these are not, you know, like lots of big people so
It's pretty hilarious
And so I broke down and I just ordered season 10 like all the hot sauces and I have them downstairs
In my kitchen on display just waiting for my next wing night
where I will be going through and eating all 10 of the wings in a row in
escalating order of hot spiciness. I gotta say I didn't even know about that
but that is a much better podcast than what we're doing here because anyone can
drink beer and not flame out well not everyone but well maybe next maybe we
should have friends with beer and a wing next time you know maybe yeah or maybe
we should set something on fire and eat it that sounds even better on that
On that note, I think this is a good point, a good time for us to wrap up this show.
What do you think?
I think so too.
So if folks want to get a hold of us, I believe there's a couple of places.
I think the easiest people to remember is friendswithbeer.com.
Yeah, and I swear to God I came up.
Did I not make a Twitter account for this?
Uh, you did.
I don't remember what it is though.
But if you see...
Isn't it beer.tweetback.us, I think?
I have no idea.
But if you go to friendswithbeer.com, you will find us and you will find a link to our Twitter account, which is friendswbeerpod.
Friends with beer pod.
And I also registered another domain, but however it's going to make me sign.
You did. You did like friendswith.beer or something like that.
But I don't think people will necessarily remember that.
But they will remember friendswithbeer.com because that's easy for them to remember.
You're like Vic, you hate the clever ones.
No, I like the clever ones.
But I also know that people won't remember friendswith.beer, which, by the way, is the address that you register.
Okay. All right. Well, let me look and let me see what our Twitter one is, because it should be in my hover as well.
I said it's friendswbeerpod.
No, no, no. I registered...
So I have tweetback.me, tweetback.us, and I think I pointed beer.tweetback.us to...
Yeah, beer.tweetback.us will take you to twitter.com/friendswbeerpod.
So if it's easier to remember beer.tweetback...
Yeah, I'm sure.
... you're tweeting back at us.
.us/...
No, tweetback at us.
Tweetback at us.
See, on BubbleSort we have this whole tweetback thing.
I don't know how to start it.
Friendswithbeer.com.
Friendswithbeer.com will get you there eventually.
Yeah.
So, uh...
So, Friends with Beer.com.
Oh, anyway, as far as we can be found...
As far as you're concerned, I'm everywhere.
Right? We're everywhere.
But I think if they start at friendswithbeer.com, they'll find us.
Thanks, so too.
Well, Peter Nikolaidis, I want people to understand that it's not always gonna be yoga, AT&T, and it is always gonna be beer.
But we talk about a lot of things. We like technology.
We do.
We like... You like running. I like biking.
I like biking too.
No, no. Yeah, you do. You're a very avid mountain biker, especially.
I was mountain biking Killington this weekend.
That's right. Never kill.
You should never kill your bike. No, just did a ton of killing.
I start actually I'm wondering now that I'm doing yoga,
I bet I could do running again with much better results on my knees.
That sounds like a challenge.
I accept. Nope, I'm not going to.
I'm still going to bike.
All right. Well, this is great.
And this will hopefully be episode one.
I'm going to start editing this today.
Today, my friend.
On that note, I think it's time to push the big red button.
Inconceivable!